{
    "educationCourse": {
        "nameOfCourse": "Universe",
        "topics": [
            {
                "topicName": "Solar System",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Quantity of planets",
                        "answers": [6,7,8,9],
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Our natural satellite",
                        "answers": [
                            "moon",
                            "titan",
                            "phoenix",
                            "num"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Biggest planet in system",
                        "answers": [
                            "earth",
                            "jupiter",
                            "saturn",
                            "neptun"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "topicName": "Galaxies",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Name of our galaxy",
                        "answers": [
                            "milky way",
                            "coffe break",
                            "time to tea",
                            "claster phoenix"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Nearest galaxy",
                        "answers": [
                            "artemida",
                            "claster phoenix",
                            "andromeda",
                            "stolpy sozidaniya"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "What in center of galaxy",
                        "answers": [
                            "orange soda",
                            "red line",
                            "lost bkb",
                            "black hole"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Form of many galaxies",
                        "answers": [
                            "pyramid",
                            "spiral",
                            "cube",
                            "ball"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "topicName": "Planet Earth",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "How many seas on planet",
                        "answers": [
                            "30",
                            "40",
                            "50",
                            "bigger"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 4
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "How many mainlands",
                        "answers": [
                            "6",
                            "7",
                            "8",
                            "9"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 1
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Biggest mainland",
                        "answers": [
                            "north America",
                            "Eurasia",
                            "Australia",
                            "south America"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 2
                    },
                    {
                        "textOfQuestion": "Where is Heops pyramid?",
                        "answers": [
                            "on Earth",
                            "in air",
                            "in Giza",
                            "under water"
                        ],
                        "correctAnswer": 3
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
}